omegatheme.com 2017-03-20

# Privacy Policy - OmegaTheme.com

This privacy policy sets out how Omegatheme uses and protects any information that you give Omegatheme when you use this website. Omegatheme is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. We should ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

##   
1\. General information

Omegatheme may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

##   
2\. Information collection and use

  * You may decide whether to proceed with any activity that requests personally identifiable information. If you do not wish to provide the requested information, however, you may not be able to complete the (purchase) transaction.
  * We do not collect information from individuals under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, we ask that you do not provide any personal information through this site. If we have specific knowledge that an individual under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information to this site, we will remove such information without any notification.
  * Policy for types of information:

###   
Registration and Product Order Information

Omegatheme will ask you for certain personally identifiable information as part of the registration / purchasing process such as: name and contact information including email address; demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests; other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.

###   
Credit Card Information

If you use a credit card to purchase products via this site, your name as it appears on the credit card, the credit card number, expiration date and billing address will be encrypted as it passes over the Internet. Omegatheme does not record or keep your credit card information for online credit-card transactions; rather such information is simply passed through to our contracted payment processing vendor (PayPal, MoneyBookers, etc.). Omegatheme may access such information through the payment processing company, but does not do so except to process refunds or adjustments and to the extent necessary in the event of nonpayment or disputed payments, or as may be necessary for Omegatheme' compliance, in Omegatheme' discretion, with applicable law.

### Information for Technical Support

When we get your request for online technical support, we will ask you for necessary information to complete the transaction such as your name, email address and information about your computer hardware, software, hosting and the nature of the problem you are experiencing. Such transmissions and storing of your data are secure.

## 3\. Security of Your Information

We are committed to ensuring that your all information is secure. The Site is regularly tested for security breaches to ensure that all information collected is secure from unauthorized viewing. 

## 4\. Site Functionality

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. Once you close your browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our Site. You may still use our Site if you reject the cookie. The only drawback to this is that you will be limited in some areas of our Site. For example, you will not be able to use certain features of our forum or other parts of the Site that offer customized settings.

### Log Files

We (Omegatheme and/or our contracted web analytics provider(s)) do keep track of the domains from which you access our site and Services on the World Wide Web, and may log IP addresses or other identifiers for statistical purposes. We do this to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use to identify and analyze trends and the results ofour marketing efforts, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer the Site and Services, and analyze users' movements. We may periodically share aggregate demographic information with our business partners. IP addresses and other identifiers are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Newsletter

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address.

### Links to other websites

This Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Omegatheme, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Site.

## 5\. How we contact you

We may contact you mainly by email via the email address you provided. Your email address must be valid so we can contact you for support or product delivering.

## 6\. Changing or corectting your personal information

You are free to update your information at any time directly through our site. Please remember provide a **valid email address.**
